linkedin.com/in/ericzarycki ericzarycki.github.io ericdzarycki@gmail.com 813-951-6515

Professional Summary:

A current college senior at the University of South Florida pursuing a degree in Computer and Information Science, with a concetration in Data Science and Analytics. Internship and work experience in networking, analytics, and business.

Education:

Aug 2022 – July 2024 University of South Florida

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Computer and Information Sciences

Concetration: Data Science and Analytics

CUM GPA: 3.0 USF GPA: 3.75

Scholarships:

2021 – 2024 Citizen Band Potawatomi Scholarship

Summary of Technical Skills:

- R (Programming Language)
- SQI
- Snowflake, MySQL, DBeaver
- Python, C++

- Network troubleshooting
- Network configuration
- Cisco devices (routers, switches)
- Tableau

Work Experience:

05/2023 – 08/2023 Marketing Analytics Intern

IBM, New York, NY

- Analyzed data sets to identify customer segments, providing insights for targeted marketing strategies.
- Partnered with the broader team to align marketing efforts with identified customer segments.
- Translated data insights into actionable recommendations for optimizing marketing campaigns.

11/2022 – 02/2023 Network Switch Installer

Virtual Service Operations (VSO), US

- Traveled across the United States to install and upgrade network switches for a client, ensuring reliable network connectivity and efficient data transfer.
- Coordinated with clients and site leads to plan and execute installations, minimizing disruptions to daily operations and meeting project deadlines.
- Conducted testing and troubleshooting to ensure optimal switch performance, resolving issues in a timely and efficient manner to ensure client satisfaction.

CV: Eric Zarycki

06/2022 – 08/2022 Business Analytics Intern

Chewy, Dania Beach, FL

- Created a dashboard visualizing all active and non-active widget metrics over a specific date range or range of dates.
- Ensured that the SQL used for this project was correctly written through code reviews and additional quality checks.
- Met with various teams to go over the scope of the project and any features those teams would like to see included in the dashboard.

01/2022 ChewyCase – 2022 Virtual Case Competition – 1st Place

Chewy, Remote

- Selected as one of the 45 high-achieving students across the nation to propose the next product or service launch.
- Analyzed the company's 2020 financial reports and numerous articles to identify market trends and perform a SWOT analysis to present as a digestible deliverable to company executives.
- Proposed the winning solution of creating and monetizing a service which would potentially generate \$100M in sales within the course of five years as a result of IT implementations.

08/2021 – 03/2022 Account Support Intern

Tallo, Remote

- Carried out industry research and identified areas of opportunity for the Education and Development teams.
- Helped create and develop a marketing strategy to facilitate new user engagement, by advertising on platforms such as Instagram and LinkedIn.

Volunteer Experience:

05/2023 – Present T.E.A.M Student Mentor

University of South Florida, Hybrid

- Scheduled regular one-on-one meetings with new transfer students at USF to provide guidance and support in their academic and social goals.
- Collaborated with mentees to develop action plans for academic success, time management, and building a strong social network.

10/2022 Hackathon Volunteer

Girls in Tech, Inc., Remote

- Participated in code review sessions with participants, providing feedback and suggestions to enhance code quality and maintain best practices.
- Actively engaged with participants during the scavenger hunt, guiding and supporting them to successfully complete challenges while fostering a collaborative atmosphere.